Beloved, sometimes in our life we need something
greater than all.
On a daily basis we are bombarded by
all things, some which we cannot see, like
microbes.
Sometimes the bombardment may be spiritual, but sometimes
we need help.
I want to talk to us about a
topic, or a podcast, which I call, And
He Healed Them.
And He healed all of them, or He
healed them all.
We see that in Matthew 12, 15b.
I was talking about Jesus Christ, the Pharisees
were harassing Him, so He retired to a
far distance and the multitude followed Him.
And it says here, And He healed them
all.
I would tell you for nothing here, that
Jesus Christ is called the Balm in Gilead.
And what the Balm in Gilead does is
that He heals.
If you open your Bible, it is replete,
the Gospels are replete with how Jesus Christ
healed.
In John 10, 38 it says, How Jesus
Christ was filled with the Holy Ghost and
with power.
He went about doing good.
Healing all those who were oppressed of the
devil, for God was with Him.
I don't know what your affliction might be.
Do you need healing of an emotional kind,
after a heartbreak, after being jilted, or after
a loved one passed on?
Do you need physical healing, in other words,
you had an injury, or you need a
bone replacement or something, which the doctors need
to do?
Or is your healing, or what you're seeking
for, is it spiritual, where it's only prayer
that could render a solution?
I'll have you know that the Balm in
Gilead, who is also called the Son of
Righteousness, in keeping with Malachi 4.2, is
available.
Now, God has promised all manner of healing
through the peerless name of Jesus.
In John 14, verse 13, Jesus said, Whatsoever
you ask in my name, that I will
do, that the Father may be glorified in
the Son.
And that's why it's written that Jesus Christ
has been given a name above every other
name, that at His name, every knee should
bow, every tongue confess, whether they be in
heaven, upon the earth, or beneath the earth,
at the name of Jesus, every knee should
bow.
Thus, we see the likes of John and
Peter, in Acts chapter 3.
They were going past the beautiful gate, and
they saw this man who was begging for
alms.
And Peter looked at him, he said, Silver
and gold I have none, but in the
name of our Lord Jesus Christ, rise up
and walk.
And Peter hauled the man to his feet,
and his, his legs received strength, and he
followed them in, praise the name of the
Lord.
What about Peter's mother-in-law, in Luke
chapter 4, Jesus healed her.
Remember of course, the woman with the issue
of blood, she didn't even have to call
on Jesus, all she did was stole, was
she, she stole the miracle, the healing, in
Luke chapter 8, 43 to 48.
As soon as she touched the garment, because
of her faith, the blood that was flowing
through from her body, ceased.
Praise the name of the Lord.
What is your challenge?
The name of our Lord Jesus can do
it.
In John chapter 11, we see that Jesus
even brought a man back from the dead,
who had been dead for four days, his
name was Lazarus.
And all he said, all he did was,
thank God, he said, Father, I thank you
because you always hear me, and asked them
to roll away the stone, and he called
forth, he said, Lazarus come forth, and he
who had been dead for days, came out,
not walking, but the power in the world
brought him forth.
And he said, lose him and set him
free, because he still has his great clothes
on him.
Now that name, that personality, and the power
that attaches to his name, is available for
you.
Call on him today, ask Jesus to come
into your life, ask him to heal that
disease, ask him to heal that sickness, ask
him to remove that emotional turmoil.
And believe you me, you have a story
to tell, and a testimony to give.
God bless you all.